export const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question:  "What is React in web development?",
    choices: [
      "A JavaScript library",
      "A database management system",
      "A web browser",
      "A programming language",
    ],
    answer: "A JavaScript library",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In React, how can you pass data from a parent to a child component?",
    choices: [
      "Using 'setState'",
      "Using 'props'",
      "Using 'state'",
      "Using 'useCallBack'",
    ],
    answer: "Using 'props'",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What does React Router do?",
    choices: [
      "Manage state transitions",
      "Handle HTTP requests",
      "Create routes in a React app",
      "Implement global styles",
    ],
    answer:
      "Create routes in a React app",
  },
  // {
  //   question:
  //       "Which React hook is used to perform side effects in functional components?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "useEffect",
  //     "useEffectEffect",
  //     "useSideEffect",
  //     "performEffect",
  //   ],
  //   answer:
  //       "useEffect",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which of the following is a way to define a state in a component?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "state = {}",
  //     "this.state = {}",
  //     "useState({})",
  //     "setInitialState({})",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "useState({})",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "What is the virtual DOM in React?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "Actual browser DOM",
  //     "Lightweight representation",
  //     "HTML in-memory storage",
  //     "Visual design overlay",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Lightweight representation",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "In React Router, how can you pass parameters to a route?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "Using the params prop",
  //     "Using the query prop",
  //     "Embedding them in the route's path",
  //     "Using the data prop",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Embedding them in the route's path",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which method is used to handle user input in React?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "handleInput",
  //     "onChange",
  //     "inputHandler",
  //     "onUserInput",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "onChange",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "What is the main role of Redux in a React application?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "To style React components",
  //     "To centralize the application state",
  //     "To handle asynchronous operations",
  //     "To define React components",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "To centralize the application state",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "What problem does useContext in React help solve?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "Styling issues",
  //     "Component reusability",
  //     "Prop drilling",
  //     "State management",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Prop drilling",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "What is the role of the key prop in React lists?",
  //   choices: [
  //     "Styling identifier",
  //     "Unique component identifier",
  //     "Access control",
  //     "Event handler",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Unique component identifier",
  // },
];
